Akshay Chindaliya (1) Featured

Tableau Developer seeking roles in Application Development, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Web Intelligence, Desktop Intelligence, SAP Business Objects, Tableau, Oracle, SQL Server, IBM DB2, BEx Query, Design Studio



Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 0 Month(s) Current Designation: Software Developer

Current Company: TEKsystems Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Information Technology]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, INDIA

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Tableau Developer, Software Developer, Application Development, Application Maintenance, Project

Management, Requirement Analysis, Web Intelligence, Desktop Intelligence, SAP Business Objects, Tableau, Oracle, SQL

Server, IBM DB2, BEx Query, Design Studio

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

An erudite professional with 4 years of experience in developing reports from different data sources like Oracle, SQL Server, and Snowflake

Extensively worked on developing Tableau Dashboard in accordance with business requirement

Technical skills entails: Tableau/SAP BO/PowerBi

Expertise in designing and developing various Dashboards/ Reports with different Analytics Views, Alerts, Guided Navigation, and Interactive Dashboards using Tableau

Experience in designing stunning visualizations using Tableau software and publishing and presenting dashboards on web and desktop platforms

Used BI tools to develop reusable objects (facts, attributes, metrics, filters, hierarchies etc.) for information products including reports, documents, dashboards and scorecards

An effective communicator with excellent relationship management skills and strong analytical, problem solving & organizational capabilities

Work Experience

TEKsystems as Software Developer

Aug 2019 to Till Date

TekSystems as Tableau Developer

Aug 2019 to Sep 2020

Key Result Areas:

Developing style guide for development of BI visualizations, design of components, naming of items, data source creation and naming

Maintaining the integrity of development work and underlying data through the use of version control systems

Assessing performance, reward results, motivate and foster matrix management, Database Management and Data Modeling

Demonstrated translate a question into a visualization which provides insight and answers the question

Performing detailed data analysis such as determine the structure, content, and quality of the data through examination of source systems and data samples

Working on all aspects of the engineering of the service, including such topics as performance, testing, HA, dashboard

1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=e5a6cd7c6eb041af3938d45219559bde5b5b0e034e470f140444445155...

design & tuning

Diagnosing and responding to service desk requests regarding data integrity and functional or interactive issues in existing and future dashboards

Developing dashboards and visualizations that empower decision makers

Performing peer review of code and testing in order to detect and minimize application problems. Develop and provide training to team members and staff on basic utilization and advanced proficiencies, up to and including training others to provide backup to this role/function

Infocepts Technologies as Analyst (Tableau Developer) Jan 2018 to Jan 2019

Amtox Data as Associate (SAP BO Developer) Apr 2015 to Jan 2018

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Information Technology) from SGBAU in 2015

IT Skills

| Skill Name | Version | Last Used | Experience |
|--------------------|---------|-----------|------------|
| SAP | 4.1 | 2019 | 2 Year(s) |
| SQL | SQL | 2018 | 2 Year(s) |
| TABLEAU | 2018 | 2019 | 1 Year(s) |
| Business Objects | | | |
| Design Studio | | | |
| Oracle, SQL server | | | |
| IBM DB2, BEx Query | | | |

Languages Known

| Language | Proficiency | Read | Write | Speak |
|----------|-------------|------|-------|-------|
| English | Proficient | | | |

Projects

Project Title: Nielsen Connected System

Client: Tyson Foods

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Jun 2017 - Till Date Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: The Project is all about the Visual Insight, developed dossier for Client and meet the requirements.

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No Countries: India, Australia, Germany

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time